First time
はじめまー
Miyan-chan, I'm going to put in a head chip. You look happy.
す ミヤンちゃん、頭チップを入れますよ 嬉しそうですね
Can you go a little longer?
もう ちょっといける?
delicious?
おい しい?
Miyan
ミ ヤ ン
Chan, put it in your mouth
ちゃん 口入れて
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
Feels good
気持ちいい
Shall we go to sleep? You can put your feet up.
寝 ちゃおうか 足つけていいよ
Qi Is it okay to sway at the top?
気 上位で揺れても大丈夫?
It's amazing because you're young
若いからね すごい
I also touch my back
後 ろも手ついて
like?
好 き?
like
好き
Get behind me
後 ろになって
I'm going to cum inside you, if you keep this up, say goodbye.
中 出しちゃいますよ、このままだと バイバイして
It came out. Raise your upper body and it fell on your butt. Try touching it.
出 てきた 上半身起こして お尻に落ちちゃった 触ってみて
Is this below?
これ 下かな?
warm?
温かい?
Warm clay is expensive. How was it?
温かい 粘土が高いです どうでした?
Creampie feels so good, it felt amazing, it felt so good.
中出しは 気持ちいい すごいね 感じてましたね 気持ちいい
It's still inside, I'll add it.
まだ 中にありますね 書き足しますね
A lot came out
た くさん出てきた
Let's wash and go home
洗 って帰りましょう